(Dead Mount, Death Play)
《尸体如山的死亡游戏》
(Episode 21: The Spirit)
(#21 The Spirit-精灵-)
The chief editor said he's very busy.
主编说他很忙
What should I do about the interview story today?
今天的采访该怎么办呢
Hey, you there, mister!
等一下 那边的大哥哥
You've been looking at that building, right?
你刚才在看那栋大楼吧
Could it be that you're interested in Phantom Solitaire
难道你对怪人雪天鸦
and the mysterious young diviner?
或是谜之少年占卜师感兴趣吗
What did you say?
你说什么
I see. So there's a journalist investigating Polka.
我知道了 她是正在调查 波尔卡的杂志记者吗
Maybe she can get some information.
说不定可以获得什么情报
Stay with her without letting her in on your true intentions.
你就配合她吧 但不要让她得知多余的情报
Fine. I got permission.
好吧 我得到许可了
Great, thank you!
太好了 谢谢你
Then let's get going.
那么我们出发吧
Ugh, it's so cold.
呃 好冷啊
What's this?
怎么回事
Like the cage of a wild beast.
猛兽的牢笼
It's more like the deep sensation of death
不 这种深刻的死亡的感觉
that I got when I was in the presence of a complete t'ing-fu.
就像面对刚完成的庭壶一样
It's nearby.
很近
Huh?
咦
I have a really strong urge to turn tail and go home.
不知道为什么 我超想回家的
Snap out of it!
不管了
Do you have business with Polka? Or perhaps with Xiaoyu?
你是要找波尔卡 还是要找小幽呢
But now is not a good time.
但是现在不行哦
They're still at work.
他们还在工作
Um, Miss Sakimiya, right?
那个 你是崎宫小姐吧
Huh? Kochou?
咦 胡蝶
Do you know this man?
你该不会和这位先生认识吧
Why is it so freezing here?
话说 这里好冷啊
Hmm, it might be a bit strange.
嗯 好像是有点奇怪呢
Miss Soara!
索亚拉小姐
It's you, isn't it?
就是你吧
You're the assailant who's been showing up all over the place lately.
最近那个鬼鬼祟祟的袭击者
Oh?
咦
What's this guy doing?
这个人在干什么啊
Need a hand, Arahabaki?
要我帮你吗 亚拉幅木
You're in a good mood, boss.
你心情挺好的嘛 老大
But
不过
I'll clean up my own mess.
自己的烂摊子我会自己收拾
Yeah?
是吗
I thought I'd strangled everyone around the building to keep us from being seen.
为了不暴露存在 大楼周围的家伙 我应该已经全部干掉了才对
But now the boss has shown up?
看来那些家伙的头目终于出现了啊
Taipei's made contact with the cell phone thief.
太贝跟手机小偷发生接触
Round one begins.
第一回合
What? Are you sure about that?
什么 你确定对手的身份了吗
The uniforms of Heilei operatives are soaked in a special fragrant oil.
黑雷部队的衣服上涂有特殊的香油
If she came close enough to strangle them,
如果发生了殊死搏斗
the smell should be strong enough
其味道就会沾染到对手身上
to last even after bathing.
这个味道就算每天洗澡也洗不掉
Taipei's sense of smell could track it down even after ten days.
太贝的嗅觉能追踪这个气味长达十天
Why is he so eager to attack her?
为什么他要急着攻击对方
To eliminate the enemies around the young lady and her associates.
为了排除出现在 大小姐他们身边的敌人
Of course, this is just an excuse.
这当然只是借口
His rationale is more base than an animal's.
那家伙比野兽还要没有理性
He just wants a death match against a powerful opponent.
他只想跟强者斗个你死我活
Hey, hey. What is this?
喂喂 怎么了怎么了
What's that sound?
什么声音
Young lady, it's very dangerous here. Please stay in your room.
大小姐 这里很危险 请你待在房间
Darn it.
可恶
What on earth is Taipei doing?
太贝那家伙到底想干什么
The clients have been led out.
我已经将客人引导出去了
FORTUNE-TELLING As long as Takumi is in his room,
(占卜) 匠只要待在房间里
he should be all right.
应该就是安全的
We going to help out either one of them?
我们要帮哪边呢
First, get the journalist out of here.
总之 先把记者小姐带到外面去吧
Okay.
好
She remains unfazed in the face of such a situation.
面对这种情况还能不为所动
Could she also be a Shinoyama bodyguard?
她也是四乃山的护卫吗
Let alone her.
且不说她
The Shinoyama have some fine pawns on their side.
四乃山可真是有不少好帮手啊
Lord Civil?
塞维利亚大人
-Lulu. -Y-Yes?
-露露 -在 我在
Come on, it's dangerous here.
好啦 这里很危险 很危险唷
This exclusive news is too good to pass up.
我不能放过这种独家新闻
At least one shot.
至少让我拍一张
This way of using magic…
刚刚那人使用魔力的方式…
Mr. Sabaramond?
塞巴拉隆多先生
Watch closely.
你好好看着
That's the workaround used by those who cannot speak with elves
那是不能与精灵交流的家伙
to force the magic out of them instead.
将魔力强行抽出的秘技
They take the elf's magic directly into their bodies
他们会从精灵身上夺取魔力
and fill their own "vessel" with it.
填充在自己的容器里
If they can't withstand the magic they steal from the elf,
如果承受不了抢夺过来的魔力
their bodies will be contorted, ruptured, and fried.
作为代价 术士的身体 就会扭曲变形并四分五裂
An elf eater.
真不愧是精灵猎食者
The first rank Imperial Court Sorcerer.
宫廷魔法师第一席
Arius Sabaramond is indeed well-deserved.
亚里乌斯塞巴拉隆多果真名不虚传
Haha.
哈哈
You are mean, Easlies.
你说话可真难听呢 伊斯莉丝
I certainly did not eat them.
我可没有把它们吃掉
I just temporarily borrow the circulating power in this world.
我只是暂时借用了一下 循环于这世上的力量而已
Corpse God.
尸神殿
I envy you.
我很羡慕你
You are loved by many,
你被他人所爱
including countless spirits,
被众多的灵魂们所爱
and even loved by witches who hate mankind.
甚至被厌恶人类的魔女所爱
I hope you love them too.
你也可以将爱给予他人
As many people as you can
给予众多的人
and the countless world.
众多的世界
Love is the miracle that can conquer all else.
爱才是能够战胜一切事物的奇迹
I can't get a handle on love.
我无法掌握爱
And so, all I can do
所以我只能
BYANDY EMPIRE, FIRST-RANK IMPERIAL COURT SORCERER pine for the world.
(巴亚蒂帝国宫廷魔术师第一席) 苦苦爱慕着这个世界
ARIUS SABARAMOND
(亚里乌斯塞巴拉隆多)
Alright, let's go back.
好了 我们回去吧
This is to cover the damage.
这个给你 就算是各种赔偿吧
I can't accept something so…
我不能收下 这…
Tsk.
可恶
Darn it. I was careless.
真是的 我太大意了
After you got him with that, boss,
如果他中了老大的那招
at least a few of his organs must be thrashed.
他的内脏应该受损了好几处才对
Didn't you dodge it?
你不是躲开了吗
Tsk.
可恶
I am, after all, your bodyguard, boss.
我好歹也是老大你的护卫啊
What?
什么
This is
这是…
the same treatment the imperial assassination unit would give.
跟帝国暗杀部队一样的处置方式
You've had to see some pretty messed-up stuff.
刚才不小心让你看到了 一些不太好的东西
But you're calm.
不过你还真是冷静呢
Oh.
对了
I still have my face frozen using the "false face" spell.
误认相貌魔法 到现在还在伪装着我的表情
Due to my frequent peeking into others' fates, I am used to it.
由于我经常窥探他人的命运 所以这种事我已经习以为常了
I see.
原来如此
I guess Mikoto's evaluation was on point.
水琴的眼光果真不错
Anyway, I won't cause you any more trouble.
好了 我就不再给你添麻烦了
At least not here.
不过 仅限于这里
Arahabaki, I leave Lulu to you.
亚拉幅木 露露就拜托你了
-Okay! -O-Okay.
-好的 -哇 好
Is it over?
结束了吗
Seems so.
算是吧
I've never experienced an attack like that in my life.
我从未遭受过这样的攻击
What did that guy do to me?
那人对我做了什么
What was with that customer just now?
刚才那位客人是怎么回事
A product of Sabaramond.
塞巴拉隆多的产物
I'm certain he's a member of that organization Fire-breathing Bug was talking about.
他毫无疑问就是 赴火之虫提到的那个组织的人
What makes you so sure?
你为什么这么肯定
His face brought back memories.
我看到了一张令人怀念的脸孔
But it's not really him.
但他并不是那个人
Because the color of the soul is different.
因为灵魂的颜色不一样
And he's younger than that person was.
而且他还比那个人年轻
But the way he used magic
可是 他使用魔法的方式
was too similar to call him a stranger.
实在是太像那个人了
Similar to who?
像谁
The former head of the imperial court sorcerers,
曾经是宫廷魔法师首席的
Arius Sabaramond.
亚里乌斯塞巴拉隆多先生
Huh?
咦
Why'd you deal with him? You could've just left him to me.
真是的 你为什么要出手啊 明明交给我就好了
Sorry I snatched your prey from you.
抢了你的猎物真是抱歉呢
I was just about to get a big fight.
我好不容易要动真格了呢
Sorry, sorry.
抱歉抱歉
I just figured it's okay not to hide my power anymore.
因为我觉得我没必要 再隐藏自己的力量了
Take this.
这个给你
Huh? What am I going to do with your passport, boss?
老大你的护照怎么了吗
CIVIL A SABARAMONDO Immigration paperwork is done using my full name.
(塞维利亚亚里乌斯塞巴拉隆多) 入境手续我是用全名办的
So it's written right there.
所以我的全名就写在这上面
An organization uses my surname without permission.
我的姓氏被某些人 擅自用来当作组织的名字
The name Sabaramond.
就是塞巴拉隆多
Those geezers in the organization went wild after they discovered this.
组织里的老人们 在发现这个后可是闹得很厉害呢
Hey, guys.
嗨 各位
Have you heard of products of Sabaramond?
你们知道塞巴拉隆多的产物吗
They are the villains who recently shot at Phantom Solitaire
就是之前狙击了怪人雪天鸦
and infiltrated the police.
并入侵了警察局的坏蛋们
Word has it that the people Fire-breathing Bug has been burning
据说那个赴火之虫一直以来所烧的人
are comrades of these guys.
就是那群坏蛋的同伙
Anyone who knows the truth,
知道真相的人
please comment
请在雪天鸦TV
SOLITAIRE TV on this channel, Solitaire TV.
(雪天鸦TV) 这个频道的下方留言
Wow. No mistaking it.
啊 没错
IDOL, KANNAGI RYOUMA This is a video of my concert.
(偶像 神薙凉马) 这是我开演唱会时的视频
But the face and voice belong to someone I don't recognize. That's so weird.
但我的脸和声音却变成了陌生人 真是不可思议
It's what they call a deep fake.
这就是那个叫AI换脸的技术吧
They used CG to swap the face and voice with someone else's.
可以用CG将脸和声音换成其他人
But who is this guy?
可是这个人又是谁呢
Solitaire's son?
是雪天鸦的儿子吗
And he mentioned "Sabaramond"…
他说的是塞巴拉隆多是…
TRENDING, SABARAMOND Oh, it's already trending.
(热搜话题 塞巴拉隆多) 哎呀 已经上热搜了
I see.
原来如此
No wonder the old farts at headquarters are freaking out about this.
难怪总部的老头子们会大呼小叫的了
Right?
对吧
My name being registered at immigration links it back to us too.
毕竟我在入境管理局写了自己的名字 跟我扯上关系也是在所难免
By the way, was that such a good idea?
话说 那些宝石
Giving that diviner those jewels?
真的可以送给那个占卜师吗
Yeah, it's okay.
嗯 没事的
Though, right about now, he's probably realized he's lost out big on the deal.
不过对方现在应该 也觉得遭受了巨大的损失
I knew it. He's gone!
他果然不见了
Huh? What happened?
唔 你怎么了
I can still detect his soul.
我还可以感知到他的灵魂
No doubt about it. He's been kidnapped.
毫无疑问 他被对方抓走了
It seems they made quite a show of beating you up.
你好像被对方狠狠地打倒了呢
My apologies.
非常抱歉
Don't worry about it.
不 没关系
Thanks to that, we know the face of our enemy.
多亏你 敌人的伪装也因此暴露了
It's our turn to corner them.
这次轮到我们将对方逼入绝境了
Um, is it really okay for us to take this?
那个 我们把这个拿走真的没关系吗
Those jewels were meant to cover the cost of this too.
反正那些宝石也包括这个的赔偿了
I look forward to him coming to get it back.
而且我也很期待 他能前来找我要回这个玩偶
Right?
对吧
SO SHOCKED AND FROZEN SHARK
(由于太过震惊而当机的鲨鱼)
Why are you talking to a stuffed animal?
你为什么要对着玩偶说话啊
You never know. Our fellow folk from back home
说不定来自同乡的客人
might be able to hear us through this stuffed animal.
可以通过这个玩偶听到我们的声音
Huh?
啥
I asked Lulu.
我问过露露了
I asked who the elves most strongly turned their attention toward.
我问她精灵对谁最感兴趣
The elves showed no interest in humans.
精灵大人没有对那些人类感兴趣
Instead, they were calling out something to this stuffed shark the whole time.
反而一直都在 对这个鲨鱼玩偶说些什么
The guidance of the elves is always so abstract.
精灵的指引总是这么抽象
But never once has it come to nothing.
但精灵却从来不会给出无意义的指引
It's possible that Polka Shinoyama is under the influence of a visitor
四乃山波尔卡恐怕受到了 来自同乡的客人
from another world, or, in other words, an otherworldly sorcerer.
也就是来自异世界魔法师的某种影响
BINGO
(正确)
And the fact
而且
that the elves took an interest in this means it might be a catalyst.
精灵对它感兴趣 代表它也许就是那个媒介
A catalyst?
媒介吗
Even though he went to such elaborate lengths to dress as a fortune-teller,
明明换上了那么讲究的占卜师造型
isn't it strange he would carry this shark around on his person like that?
可他却总是将那个鲨鱼带在身边 这很奇怪吧
Could something have been delivering directions to
那么 那边的人可能就是 通过这个玩偶
Polka Shinoyama through this stuffed animal?
来向四乃山波尔卡下达某种指令的
I can't be sure until I know more.
虽然还需要进一步调查才能确认这点
But I'm almost certain
但我可以确定的是
this thing is a vital key connecting
这个玩偶是将那个魔法师
the sorcerer to Polka Shinoyama.
和四乃山波尔卡联系起来的关键
YOU'RE RIGHT ON THE MARK AND YET TOTALLY OFF
(到底是什么呢) (好像对了但又没对)
In which case,
如果是这样的话
I have to look into this.
我就得好好调查一下它了
And at the same time, we have to protect it.
而且我还得保护好它
Protect it?
保护吗
If this shark can truly link us
如果这个鲨鱼真的能将我们
to the other side of the sky,
与天空的彼端连接起来的话
then it might be the first to be burned by the bug.
那群虫子说不定会急着将其烧毁
Why would that guy kidnap him?
为什么会落在那家伙手里了
I don't know.
我不知道
But it seems they haven't realized it is the real Polka.
不过看样子 对方并没有意识到 那就是真正的波尔卡
Anyway, I detected his location and put up a lookout.
总之我已经感知到对方的位置 并派东西去监视了
We have to figure out a way to save him.
得想个办法去救他才行
May I have a moment, young master Polka?
可以打扰您一下吗 波尔卡少爷
Um, I want to talk to you too.
那个 我也有事找你
Miss Kochou?
胡蝶小姐
I'm very sorry.
非常抱歉
I just went and brought this weirdo in.
我总是带来一些奇怪的家伙
Weirdo…
奇怪…
So it's because of you that he came here.
原来他是被胡蝶小姐你带来的啊
Why did you attack that guy earlier?
你刚才为什么要攻击那个人呢
Not important. Pay it no mind.
只是一点小事罢了 请不必在意
Of course he's going to mind!
怎么可能不在意啊
Just who were those people?
话说他们到底是什么人啊
Young Master Polka.
波尔卡少爷
I'd like to ask you for a reading on this.
我也想请您占卜一下此事
FORTUNE-TELLING
(占卜)
TAKERU SHINOYAMA Polka? It's me.
(四乃山尊) 波尔卡吗 是我
Mr. Takeru?
尊先生
Takeru?
尊
The head of Shinoyama Security…
是四乃山警备的…
I've heard about the matter.
事情经过我已经听说了
Those who attacked members of my company before are very dangerous.
袭击过我们公司员工的那些家伙 实在是非常危险
The reason Taipei suddenly went on the offensive was
太贝之所以突然与对方交战
because he feared something might happen to you.
也是怕你有个什么万一
Well, it seems his concerns were misplaced.
不过 现在看来似乎是我杞人忧天了
I see.
这样啊
Thank you for your concern.
有劳您费心了
And so, I would like you to divine
那么 我想拜托你占卜一下
who these people are.
那些家伙的真实身份
Understood.
我知道了
I'm not very good at finding people,
虽然我并不擅长找人
but I'll see if there are any clues.
但我会试着找看看有没有线索
And one other thing.
在那之前还有一件事
Solitaire uploaded a strange video.
雪天鸦上传了一段奇怪的视频
What?
什么
Anyone who knows the truth,
知道真相的人
please comment on this channel, Solitaire TV.
请在雪天鸦TV这个频道的下方留言
Hehehe. What do you think? Not bad, huh?
哼哼哼 怎么样 我做得不错吧
Why did you go with this footage?
你为什么要做这种视频
A certain Sabaramond gang
如果知道你是同伙
will be surprised if you're one of them, won't they?
塞巴拉隆多什么的家伙 想必也会大吃一惊吧
Perhaps, and?
也许吧 然后呢
Are you implying I need another reason?
难道还需要别的理由吗
Ah! What is with this guy?
这个人到底是怎么回事啊
I finally see your human side.
终于在你身上看到人性了
That's the first time I've yelled like that since kindergarten.
我上次这样大吼大叫 还是在上幼稚园的时候
I-I see.
是 是吗
That was fast. He switched modes in a heartbeat.
好快 他变脸好快啊
Even if I could escape safely from here,
就算我能平安从这里逃出去
I'd have to get plastic surgery and go on the lam.
我也需要整形并远走高飞才行
Is that a confession?
你承认了吗
That you're a comrade of those Sabaramond?
承认你就是塞巴拉隆多什么的同伙了
Comrade? I wonder what they think of me.
同伙吗 我不知道对方是怎么想的
I'm just their errand boy.
我只是个听命办事的人而已
Fire-breathing Bug.
赴火之虫
Why have you been going around for 100 years
你们为什么从100年前
burning those associated with Sabaramond?
就开始到处放火烧死 跟塞巴拉隆多有关的人呢
I don't even know this.
就连这件事我也都不知道
Hey, guys.
嗨 各位
Have you heard of products of Sabaramond?
你们知道塞巴拉隆多的产物吗
Even though they've been burning things for 100 years…
明明都持续烧了100年
When they do act, it's so sudden.
可他们行动起来还真是突然呢
Those children have probably caught on by now…
看来那些孩子也终于注意到了吧
that revenge should be taken indirectly to tear down everything from behind.
复仇是需要绕到对方的背后 并一口气摧毁对方的
In which case, I'll act too. Let's dance.
那么我也随之行动 并舞动起来吧
We'll welcome my little kid-assassin and our new family member,
为了迎接少年暗杀者和我的新家人
Miss Misaki.
美咲小姐
A hundred years?
持续烧了100年吗
So does that mean most of them are over 100 years old?
也就是说你们之中的人 几乎已经超过100岁了吗
No.
不是的
We are…about to disappear…from this world.
我们…很快…就要… 从这个世界上…消失了
So, we are…
所以…我们是
not meant…to exist. Errors…Flaws.
不存在…过错与…污秽之人
Bugs.
缺陷…缺陷
Non-existent…burn marks.
不存在的烧痕
We are the same…as the products.
我们和他们…与产物们是同样的
We are bugs…scorched into…the world.
都只是…烧附于这世上的虫子而已
Fire-breathing Bug has been operating for over a hundred years.
赴火之虫在100多年前开始 就一直在活动了
So, what we need to figure out is
那么我们需要查明的是
why they hold such hostility towards the Sabaramond organization.
为什么他们会仇视 塞巴拉隆多这个组织
IN ANOTHER GARAGE ON THE WEST SIDE But…
(在西侧的另一个车库里…) 但是…
Leader.
系长
I found a case that resembles this one.
我发现类似的事件了
Oh, good job, Kayakusa.
哦 你做得很好 萱草
Assuming Fire-breathing Bug's use of fire seems to be
假如赴火之虫并不是为了 满足内心的愉悦感
more than a sick fascination,
而执着于火的话
I figured whatever drives their revenge might have to do with fire at its root.
我想他们的复仇是不是 在根本上与火有某种关联
We might've hit the jackpot here.
也许就是这样
What is this?
这是什么
A fire in Shinjuku a hundred years ago?
100年前发生在新宿的火灾
16 bodies were found in the charred ruins of what appeared
在多个疑似禁闭室的火灾废墟中
to be multiple joined jail cells.
发现了男女共16具遗体
Half of them are the bodies of young children.
有一半是孩子的遗体吗
Disgusting.
真是令人难受
It's odd.
好奇怪啊
No one mentioned that
这么重大的火灾
for a major fire.
我们却居然一次也没有 听别人提起过 这不是很奇怪吗
Yes, indeed.
确实
This was in the police records,
这是警察的资料
but was it reported in the media back then?
但这件事有被报道过吗
Go look through any newspapers and major magazines from that time.
你去找找当时的报纸和大众杂志吧
Yes, sir.
是
Arase and I will look into that Higuro.
荒濑和我就去找冰黑那个家伙
What's the matter?
怎么了
WICKED SMILE
(坏笑)
What's got into you?
你到底怎么了
No, sorry.
没事 抱歉
My emotions just malfunctioned for a moment.
我的感情发生了一点交通事故
Arase…?
荒濑竟然会…
It looks like there is a connection
雪天鸦似乎跟那个组织
SOLITAIRE TV between Solitaire and that organization.
(雪天鸦TV) 已经建立了联系
My emotions have collapsed.
我的情感崩溃了
It seems it will take some time to reboot.
看样子我需要花点时间来重启
Who is this guy?
这个人是谁
I knew Solitaire was searching for Sabaramond too,
虽然我知道雪天鸦 也正在寻找塞巴拉隆多
but has he still not made contact with those three?
但他还没有接触过刚才那三个人吗
If the word "Sabaramond" is widely known, then it will become impossible to tell
如果塞巴拉隆多这个名字已经传开了
whether someone claiming that name is real or an impostor.
那我们不就无法区分 那些自称是他们的人是真是假了吗
What on earth is he thinking?
他到底在想些什么啊
NO PLAN
(无计划)
Let's set aside this matter for now.
这件事暂且不提 关于占卜的事
I have to get ready for the divination.
我需要准备一下
So,
所以
how about we meet again in the evening three days from now?
不如三天后的傍晚 你再来进行占卜如何
So he will have to adjust before telling me about them?
也就是说 在告诉我他们的情况之前 他还需要做一些调整吗
If he aims to bargain with that foreign party, then…
如果他是要偷偷地 跟那些外国人串通的话…
His mother,
那家伙的母亲
Lady Kanon…
卡农大人…
Anyway, Taipei, weren't you about to have your fortune told for a magazine article?
现在太贝为了采访 正在接受占卜对吧
I wouldn't mind if that journalist agreed.
如果那位记者同意的话 我是不介意的
He's turning the choice over to me?
咦 他把问题甩给我了吗
But this might be a good opportunity.
不过 这也许是个好机会
Solitaire and Sabaramond are linked to this building,
雪天鸦 塞巴拉隆多这个组织
or more specifically, the Shinoyama family.
都跟这栋大楼 或者说是跟四乃山家有关系
I need time to investigate.
我需要时间来调查
I don't mind either.
我也不介意
So what do you say to six p.m. three days from now?
三天后的傍晚六点可以吗
Understood. See you then.
我知道了 那到时候再见
If we're done talking, then I'll take my leave now.
既然已经谈妥了 那我就说到这里吧
Goodbye, Polka.
再见 波尔卡
Oh, yes.
啊 好的
Taipei, return to the office for now so we can have your injuries checked out.
太贝 你回来检查一下受伤的地方
Yes.
遵命
Bao, in the following three days,
暴 接下来的三天
you go and monitor Polka's movements.
你去调查一下波尔卡的动向
Roger.
收到
I leave Sayo to that bodyguard.
小夜就交给那个护卫了
-Yochigi. -Yes?
-蓬 -在
Find me the three people. Don't make any moves.
你去找那三个人 不用出手
Just get a fix on their comings and goings.
只需掌握他们的动向即可
Yes, sir.
收到
Try to acquire information from Polka
我就从波尔卡身上获取情报吧
about what they're after.
他们的目的是什么
We must also conduct our own investigation.
我们这边也需要调查一下
If situation permits,
根据情况
they may make useful pawns for us.
他们说不定能成为我们这边的人
Not only did you call us here so suddenly,
明明是你们突然把我叫出来的
but this isn't exactly the warmest welcome.
但你们欢迎我的方式还真没教养呢
About my impressions of that funny video,
关于那个有趣视频的感想
I'd already told you in my email.
我已经发邮件过去了
This is a message from the elders.
长老们要我转告您
Lord Civil, they demand you leave the country at once and go into hiding.
请塞维利亚大人您 迅速离开这个国家并躲藏起来
And if I refuse?
我要是不答应呢
Now that Lord Habaki is missing,
幅木大人已经失踪
we take our orders from the elders.
如今我们的指挥权在长老那里
Huh? You want this to get violent?
咦 你们要来硬的吗
We don't think that we can win against you, Lord Civil, or Arahabaki.
我们并不认为自己能赢得了 塞维利亚大人您和亚拉幅木
But
但是
surely you want to avoid a stray bullet accidentally hitting your attendant.
刀枪无眼 我们也不想 误伤了您的侍从
Um. It's dangerous, so please stop this.
那个 很危险的 请您别这样…
You fools.
真是愚蠢啊
How dare you point a weapon at Lulu.
你们竟敢对露露以武器相向
I-Is this your power at work, Lord Civil?
这 这也是 塞维利亚大人的力量吗
Huh? You don't know?
咦 难道说你们不知道吗
What?
咦
Can't we go save the real Polka yet?
我们现在还不能去救真正的波尔卡吗
Yes. If we rush in carelessly, it'll only blow up in our faces.
嗯 轻举妄动的话 说不定反而会让我们得不偿失
Especially that little girl who was with them.
特别是他身边那个小个子的女孩
She's possessed by an elf.
她身上附有精灵
Even with just the one she has, she might be able to destroy the entire city.
说不定仅凭这一只精灵 就能毁灭掉整个城市了
The elders are so cold.
长老们也真是无情啊
I get wanting to keep your trump card under wraps,
就算是王牌
but to think they'd keep elf a secret from their own men.
也没必要对自己人也隐瞒精灵的事吧
Don't! Don't kill them!
不可以 不可以杀他们
Almighty elf!
精灵大人
(Episode 22: The Karma)
(#22 The Karma-宿缘-)